<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Just Random Notes</title>
    <link>https://00derek.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Just Random Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 12:00:16 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://00derek.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Questions I should review myself</title>
      <link>https://00derek.github.io/posts/questions_collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 12:00:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00derek.github.io/posts/questions_collection/</guid>
      <description>Various questions and quotes that I collected and for myself to introspect and review later.
Constantly updating. It&amp;rsquo;s NOT original &amp;ndash; credits to all the original authors, even I don&amp;rsquo;t quote you here (being too lazy).
Examine your true north  I want to ______[What] so that I can _______ [why] by _______[how] What are you optimizing for? and why?  Is this essential? Am I progressing? Why am I taking this so seriously?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create blog with GH pages/Hugo</title>
      <link>https://00derek.github.io/posts/hugo_site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 20:35:52 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00derek.github.io/posts/hugo_site/</guid>
      <description>Github setup I have a corporate account and wanted to use my personal account for hosting my blog. So essentially it could be using 2 different SSH key and auth with separate keys &amp;ndash; since I have my company auth with OSXKeychain, I just did it for my personal one, and it will be the same for another account if I need it
  Create SSH keys
$ cd ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://00derek.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 12:16:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00derek.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>A father, a husband, an athlete, a software engineer, a voracious reader
Professional experience Lead Software Engineer, Exabeam Inc., CA US, Jan 2019 - Present  Lead various members to implement and improve Data Lake data lifecycle management features, also:  lead python3 migrations introduce data lifecycle management API for enabling Ops team and improved internal health checks improved unit-testing coverage with styling enforcement and automation improved documentation to help onboard new devs   Lead various resource management and stability improvement initiatives that helps cost-cutting for the SaaS deployment, optimizing performance and stability of Data Lake Simplified and streamlined deployment Ansible playbooks Pilot unified Exabeam data processing pipeline integration project  Tech stack includes: Python, Ansible, mongoDB, Kafka, Elasticsearch, Scala, Akka</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Python Dev Env setup</title>
      <link>https://00derek.github.io/posts/dev-env-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 11:35:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00derek.github.io/posts/dev-env-setup/</guid>
      <description>Making a note to jot down the tools I preferred to use when setting up Python development environment &amp;ndash; there should be one&amp;ndash; and preferably only one &amp;ndash;obvious way to do things
Terminal/REPL/IDE  zsh/oh-my-zsh https://ohmyz.sh/  plugins=(git history-substring-search zsh-autosuggestions) theme: power10k Cheatsheet   iTerm2 iPython/bpython VsCode  Python environment management   Managing virtualenv — virtualenv/virtualenvwrapper or venv manages virtual environments for a specific Python version.
  Managing multiple Python versions With pyenv</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prologue</title>
      <link>https://00derek.github.io/posts/prologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 08:47:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://00derek.github.io/posts/prologue/</guid>
      <description>Why Now my notes are all collected through Notion, I highly recommend it. But I think it may be also good to publish my notes somewhere 1. just in case 2. someone may find it helpful 3. Because I want to?
Who Anyone? Leave me your comments.
What I guess it will be mainly technical notes for now, I haven&amp;rsquo;t given a lot of thoughts of what to journal yet. So yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s random stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
